logicalexpressions.com 2012-05-14

# Logical Expressions Privacy Policy

**Check out what readers  
say about our writing...**

#114"Thank you for sharing how to create business cards using Word. I've been struggling to create a simple business card for myself for some time. Really appreciate it!"\- A.A.

| 

## Privacy Policy

At Logical Expressions, we know that you value your privacy, so we want you to know that your personal information is completely confidential. This privacy policy applies not only to our main Logical Expressions site ([http://www.logicalexpressions.com](http://www.logicalexpressions.com/)), but also to the other sites we produce, including (but not limited to):

  * The LEI Store - [http://shop.logicalexpressions.com](http://shop.logicalexpressions.com/)
  * LEI Forum & Blog - [http://forum.logicalexpressions.com](http://forum.logicalexpressions.com/) & [http://blog.logicalexpressions.com](http://blog.logicalexpressions.com/)
  * IdeaWeaver Software - [ http://www.ideaweaversoftware.com](http://www.ideaweaversoftware.com/)
  * Self-Publishers Online Conference - [http://www.SelfPublishersOnlineConference.com](http://www.selfpublishersonlineconference.com/)
  * Self Pub U - [http://www.SelfPubU.com](http://www.selfpubu.com/)
  * National Association of Pet Rescue Professionals - [http://www.naprp.com](http://www.naprp.com/)
  * Computor Companion - [ http://www.computorcompanion.com](http://www.computorcompanion.com/)
  * Logical Tips (CC Tips) - [ http://www.logicaltips.com](http://www.logicaltips.com/)
  * Many Veggie Recipes - [ http://www.manyveggierecipes.com](http://www.manyveggierecipes.com/)
  * Pet Tails - [http://www.pet-tails.com](http://www.pet-tails.com/)
  * Nerdy Musings - [http://www.nerdymusings.com](http://www.nerdymusings.com/)
  * Newsletter Help - [http://www.newsletterhelp.com](http://www.newsletterhelp.com/)
  * Technohomesteading - [ http://www.technohomesteading.com](http://www.technohomesteading.com/)
  * Web Business Success (book) - [ http://www.logicalebiz.com](http://www.logicalebiz.com/)
  * Vegan Success (book) - [http://www.vegansuccess.com](http://www.vegansuccess.com/)
  * Happy Hound (book) - [http://www.happyhoundbook.com](http://www.happyhoundbook.com/)
  * Happy Tabby (book) - [http://www.happytabbybook.com](http://www.happytabbybook.com/)
  * Publishize (book) - [http://www.publishize.com](http://www.publishize.com/)
  * Logical Tips Series (books) - [http://www.logicalguides.com](http://www.logicalguides.com/)
  * Funds to the Rescue (book) - [http://www.fundstotherescue.com](http://www.fundstotherescue.com/)

To send you an e-zine or sell you a product, we need your e-mail address. However, our privacy policy is very simple: we will never rent, sell, or give away your name, e-mail address, or other personal information to anyone else.

Similarly, if you send us an e-mail, we use your return email addresses to answer the e-mail. However, we don't use your address for any other purpose and we absolutely do not share it with any outside parties.

If you decide you want to stop receiving an e-zine, you can always "opt-out." The unsubscribe instructions appear in every issue of the e-zine and on the Web site.

Note that LEI is the sole owner of the information collected on our sites. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via e-mail or other direct contact from you. We will not ever sell, rent, or give away this information to anyone. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via e-mail in the future to tell you about site updates, specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

## Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can opt out by contacting us via the email address or phone number given below: 

Here's a list of the information we collect and how we use it.

  * Like most sites on the Internet, all Logical Expressions, Inc. Web sites automatically track certain general information about your visit so we know how many people visit the site, which browsers they are using, what Web page they came from, and which pages they visited on our site. This information helps us monitor customer traffic and site usage to help us improve the content, design, and layout of the site. When you visit Logical Expressions, Inc., our Web server gathers this information by tracing your domain name (such as aol.com, for example) but not your e-mail address. Note that none of this information is used (or can be used) to identify you personally.
  * We use Authorize.net to process payments. So when you want to buy a book, software or otherwise pay us for something by credit card, our shopping cart will need your name, e-mail address, address, telephone number, and credit card information which we then use to fulfill your order and to deliver information to you regarding your order.
  * Although the cart collects your credit card information for payment, the information is kept strictly private and confidential. We do not store credit card numbers in our ecommerce sites.
  * Some of our advertisers may use cookies to track the fact that you clicked their link on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

## Security

We take precautions to protect your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure any information we collect online.

## Links

Our Web sites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. Most of the links open a new browser window, so it's clear you are no longer on our site. However, we do encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Feedback

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy or if you have any questions, comments, or ideas regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at:

Logical Expressions, Inc.  
311 Fox Glen Road  
Sandpoint, Idaho 83864  
Phone: 208-265-3636

Click to contact us by email

| 

#### Read Articles   
from   
The Book Consultant!

to learn how to profitably publish books.

* * *

**Check Us Out in REDBOOK!**  
[Read the article about us ](http://www.redbookmag.com/your/letting-intuition-guide-you) in _Redbook Magazine_ (photos too!) 

* * *

Logical Expressions is a proud member of the BBB Online Reliability Program

* * *

[Visit SPOC  
Live Long & Publish!](http://www.selfpublishersonlineconference.com/)  
  
---|---|---
